<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blockchain learning on</title><link>/docs/12docs/blockchain/</link><description>Recent content in Blockchain learning on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/12docs/blockchain/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CIP-1694: Cardano enters the Voltaire era</title><link>/docs/12docs/blockchain/voltaire-era/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/blockchain/voltaire-era/</guid><description>Read the article on Cardano Explorer
The IOG team prepares Cardano to enter the Voltaire era. If the topic of on-chain governance interests you, you should definitely not overlook CIP-1694. This Cardano Improvement Proposal (CIP) defines foundations for decentralized decision-making. This will be the first major step towards decentralised management of the Cardano project which will hand over a significant amount of power to the community.
TLDR # Currently, the 7 governance keys are divided between 3 entities.</description></item><item><title>Ambassadors program</title><link>/docs/12docs/blockchain/ambassador-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/blockchain/ambassador-program/</guid><description>The Cardano community is privileged to have committed members of our Ambassadors Program, which was established in 2018.
The program aims to:
Drive the adoption of Cardano Promote awareness Educate the wider community
If you would like to join this program, please visit the Cardano Ambassador Program.</description></item><item><title>Cardano addresses</title><link>/docs/12docs/blockchain/cardano-address/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/blockchain/cardano-address/</guid><description>The addresses are a blake2b-256 hash of the relevant verifying/public keys concatenated with some metadata that can be stored on the Cardano blockchain.
Shelley introduces four different types of addresses:
base addresses pointer addresses enterprise addresses reward account addresses Besides those new addresses, Shelley continues to support Byron-era bootstrap addresses and script addresses, but only the new base and pointer addresses carry stake rights. Therefore, addresses consist of some serialized data specified in the ledger specification stored in the blockchain’s blocks, e.</description></item><item><title>Consensus explained</title><link>/docs/12docs/blockchain/consensus-explained/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/blockchain/consensus-explained/</guid><description>Consensus is the process of reaching a majority opinion by everyone involved in running the blockchain. An agreement must be made on which blocks to produce, which chain to adopt and to determine the single state of the network. The consensus protocol determines how individual nodes assess the current state of the ledger system and reach a consensus.
Blockchains create consensus by allowing participants to bundle transactions that others have submitted to the system in blocks, and add them to their chain (sequence of blocks).</description></item><item><title>Creating a local testnet</title><link>/docs/12docs/blockchain/local-testnet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/blockchain/local-testnet/</guid><description>A local testnet enables developers and projects building on Cardano to test new features or functionality prior to deployment on global testnet environments. While preview and pre-production environments benefit the wider developer community, a local testnet allows the execution of a hard fork in your own setup and subsequent testing of DApp behavior.
There are several possible solutions to create a local testnet. These include the use of Plutip (a tool for private network creation) or Nix (a tool for package management and system configuration).</description></item><item><title>Daedalus wallet for the Cardano testnets</title><link>/docs/12docs/blockchain/daedalus-for-testnet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/blockchain/daedalus-for-testnet/</guid><description>Here you can download any of the special testnet-only versions of the Daedalus wallet. Please note that this wallet is for testing purposes only. It may not be fully-featured and may contain bugs.
Daedalus system requirements # Operating systems
Windows 8.1, Windows 10 (Only 64-bit Windows is supported) macOS 10.13, macOS 10.14, macOS 10.15, macOS 11.1 Linux OS Tested against: Ubuntu 18.04 LTS, Ubuntu 20.04 LTS Fedora 28 Aimed at all Linux distributions Recommended hardware requirements</description></item><item><title>Delegation</title><link>/docs/12docs/blockchain/delegation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/blockchain/delegation/</guid><description>As Cardano is a proof of stake (PoS) system, owning ada not only allows you to buy goods or services, but also confers upon you the right and obligation to participate in the protocol and create blocks. Stake delegation is a mechanism inherent in the Ouroboros protocol that allows the protocol to scale even in a setting where the set of stakeholders might be highly fragmented.
Anyone who owns ada can participate in stake delegation while retaining their spending power.</description></item><item><title>Marlowe Pioneer program</title><link>/docs/12docs/blockchain/marlowe-pioneers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/blockchain/marlowe-pioneers/</guid><description>What is the Marlowe Pioneer program? # This is a program designed to train developers and anyone interested in decentralized finance products to write financial smart contracts (such as loans, swaps, CFDs and so on) using the Marlowe product suite.
When you join this program, you will become part of a focused group of developers who will get early access to a new course built to teach you how to build, simulate, analyze, and run financial smart contracts using Marlowe.</description></item><item><title>Ouroboros overview</title><link>/docs/12docs/blockchain/ouroboros-overview/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/blockchain/ouroboros-overview/</guid><description>In mythology, Ouroboros (also, uroboros) is usually depicted as a snake (or sometimes a dragon) eating its own tail in a closed circle. The word Ouroboros itself derives from Ancient Greek, its literal meaning being &amp;rsquo;tail eating&amp;rsquo; or &amp;rsquo;tail devourer.'
As a symbol, Ouroboros represents the infinity of time flowing back unto itself, in a never-ending cycle, as if caught in an eternal loop. Ouroboros first appeared in Egypt, in 13th century BC.</description></item><item><title>Pledging and delegation options</title><link>/docs/12docs/blockchain/pledging-delegation-option/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/blockchain/pledging-delegation-option/</guid><description>Ada held on the Cardano network represents a user’s stake in the protocol, the size of which is proportional to the amount of ada held. Users who hold a stake in Cardano can earn passive rewards for validating blocks. The amount of rewards they can earn is proportional to the amount of ada they pledge or delegate to a stake pool.
There are three options ada holders can consider for delegating their stake:</description></item></channel></rss>