<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>security on</title><link>/tags/security/</link><description>Recent content in security on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 09:19:42 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Infrastructure Survey 2024</title><link>/blog/infrastructure-survey-2024/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>/blog/infrastructure-survey-2024/</guid><description>A comprehensive survey to determine how SPOs conduct their activities in support of Cardano’s operational resilience # The Infrastructure Survey 2024 was recently conducted to better understand stake pool operator (SPO) needs and challenges. The Cardano Foundation publicly hosted the survey on its Typeform account from 2 to 8 April, with SPOs invited to participate through the official SPO notification letter and the SPO announcement Telegram channel. Additionally, the Foundation conducted targeted interviews with centralized exchanges (CEXs) to gather their valuable feedback and reflect on the significance of their stake weight.</description></item><item><title>Approaching full P2P node operations</title><link>/blog/approaching-full-p2p-node-operations/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>/blog/approaching-full-p2p-node-operations/</guid><description>Peer-to-peer (P2P) networking is a key contributor to the long-term decentralization, security, and resilience of blockchains, enabling P2P communication, data synchronization, and consensus among participants.
In March 2023, Dynamic P2P automated the peer selection process. Enabled by the node v.1.35.6 release, it enhanced communication between distributed nodes, simplifying the operation of relay and block-producing nodes, and eliminating the need for static configurations and manual input from stake pool operators (SPOs).</description></item><item><title>Unlocking more opportunities with Plutus V3</title><link>/blog/unlocking-more-opportunities-with-plutus-v3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>/blog/unlocking-more-opportunities-with-plutus-v3/</guid><description>Plutus V3, now available for testing on SanchoNet, introduces advanced Plutus primitives and so provides more tools for developers and unlocks more possibilities for writing smart contracts.
Improved developer experience and smart contract adoption are critical to the flourishing smart contract landscape on Cardano. Over the past year, the emergence and growth of a host of community-built developer tooling and alternative languages have added significantly to developer options and the vibrancy of the Cardano builder ecosystem.</description></item><item><title>IOG announces strategic investment in Blockfrost</title><link>/blog/iog-announces-strategic-investment-in-blockfrost/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>/blog/iog-announces-strategic-investment-in-blockfrost/</guid><description>Since its release in 2020, Five Binaries’ Blockfrost API has grown to become a key element of Cardano infrastructure, utilized by numerous developers who require access to the blockchain without the need to run a dedicated, resource-intensive, local Cardano node. Blockfrost performs a valuable and trusted function for projects building on Cardano, offering DApp developers a cost-effective, highly scalable solution to take their applications from testing through to full deployment.</description></item><item><title>Universal Anonymous Signatures: bridging past, present, and future of anonymous authentication</title><link>/blog/universal-anonymous-signatures-bridging-past-present-and-future-of-anonymous-authentication/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>/blog/universal-anonymous-signatures-bridging-past-present-and-future-of-anonymous-authentication/</guid><description>Recently, we got the paper &amp;lsquo;Foundations of Anonymous Signatures: Formal Definitions, Simplified Requirements, and a Construction Based on General Assumptions&amp;rsquo; accepted into FC'24 – the 2024 edition of the Financial Cryptography conference. This paper presents Universal Anonymous Signatures (UAS).
We are really excited about it as, besides bridging several subfields in the domain of anonymous authentication, UAS sets the path towards what we believe could be (part of) the future of Self-Sovereign Identity and something we will definitely push for integration within the Atala offering.</description></item><item><title>Eastern Hemisphere Townhall Meeting 8</title><link>/blog/eastern-hemisphere-townhall-meeting-8/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 09:19:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>/blog/eastern-hemisphere-townhall-meeting-8/</guid><description>A great meetup where we started off talking about the upcoming Ideafest, Cardano Summit and Hackathons. A lot of familiar faces joined into an insightful discussion about Scams and Scam detection. Lead by Peter Bui. We also discussed trading bots, Social and Environmental applications and touched on Stable Coins.</description></item></channel></rss>