<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Challenge Setting on</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/</link><description>Recent content in Challenge Setting on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Atala PRISM: Launch Ecosystems</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/atala-prism-launch-ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/atala-prism-launch-ecosystem/</guid><description>Challenge Setting
Challenge Budget: ₳2,000,000
Guiding Questions : # Can we bring together stakeholders to accelerate adoption and product-market-fit?
Why is it important? # Establishing a representative stakeholders working group for a decentralized ecosystem speeds up learning and building the right solutions
What is success? # Establish key relationships and learnings early in the development cycle, leading to faster and more successful business outcomes
What are the key metrics? # In addition to having a great team, product roadmap, milestones, and execution plan we look for successful proposers to execute the following as part of the business plan :</description></item><item><title>Building on NMKR</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/building-on-nmkr/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/building-on-nmkr/</guid><description>Challenge Setting
Challenge Budget: ₳100,000
Guiding Questions : # How can we make the Cardano NFT ecosystem more accessible by creating tools that implement the NMKR Dev API?
Why is it important? # We should incentivize builders to create tools that advance the Cardano NFT space without being reliant on the tool to become cash-positive
What is success? # Multiple NFT tools implementing the NMKR Dev API have been released</description></item><item><title>DAOs ♡ Cardano</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/daos-cardano/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/daos-cardano/</guid><description>Challenge Setting
Challenge Budget: ₳1,000,000
Guiding Questions : # How can we make Cardano the go-to choice for building DAO&amp;rsquo;s? What tools can we provide to enable effective DAO&amp;rsquo;s Creation and Operation? Why is it important? # Blockchain applications have moved from currency to DeFi, to NFT and DAO&amp;rsquo;s are next
What is success? # There are no better ways to manage your DAO than to use Cardano DAO&amp;rsquo;s Applied by small Business to global communities What are the key metrics?</description></item><item><title>Developer Ecosystem - The Evolution</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/developer-ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/developer-ecosystem/</guid><description>Challenge Setting
Challenge Budget: ₳2,000,000
Guiding Questions : # How do we equip and support developers with tools and working infrastructure? How do we make Cardano their first choice when it comes to building dApps? Why is it important? # Growing a developer community that is interested buildng on Cardano increases adoption Creating as many tools and infrastructure as possible attracts developers to start exploring opportunities What is success? # Accelerated dApp development Increasing number of open source projects on Cardano What are the key metrics?</description></item><item><title>Development &amp; Infrastructure</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/development-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/development-infrastructure/</guid><description>/C++{}
Challenge Setting
Challenge Budget: ₳2,925,000
Guiding Questions : # What research, tools or software can improve the developer ecosystem or infrastructure to make it easier to build and scale on the Cardano blockchain?
Why is it important? # Developers need tools and software to more easily build and scale applications and integrations on the Cardano blockchain
What is success for the following guiding topics? # Node, SPO tools and software - Amount of adoption from other projects, metrics around any scalability, security or cost improvements.</description></item><item><title>dRep improvement and onboarding</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/drep-improvement-onbroading/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/drep-improvement-onbroading/</guid><description>Challenge Setting
Challenge Budget: ₳100,000
Guiding Questions : # How do you achieve &amp;ldquo;(1) diverse and many dRep participation + (2) easy and proper voter delegation?&amp;rdquo;
Why? # Without (1) diverse and many dRep participation ⇨ centralized. Without (2) easy and proper voter delegation ⇨ dysfunctional. What does success look like? # After one year,
(1) 200+ deReps from 100+ countries have participated. (2) 50%+ of the voters are voting “carefully” Key Metrics to measure # Diversity of dReps Did it lead to the onboarding of diverse dReps with different languages, national origins, occupations, genders, ages, religions, etc.</description></item><item><title>ODSE: Open Source Dev Ecosystem</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/open-source-dev-ecosystem/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/open-source-dev-ecosystem/</guid><description>Challenge Setting
Challenge Budget: ₳1,000,000
Guiding Questions : # Can we build a Cardano community-owned Open-Source ecosystem that’s
commercially viable to drive growth commercially viable to increase opportunities commercially viable to increase project visibility Why is it important? # Growing a marketplace and ecosystem of experts able to work on complex software is important to build and maintain the foundations of Cardano
What is success? # More open-source projects, developers, and users Improved visibility and quality of open-source projects Improved open-source infrastructure What are the key metrics?</description></item><item><title>Products &amp; Integrations</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/products-integrations/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/products-integrations/</guid><description>Challenge Setting
Challenge Budget: ₳3,000,000
Guiding Questions : # What products and integrations can be developed or improved that will offer more use cases to the Cardano ecosystem that are high impact and drive more adoption?
Why is it important? # Cardano needs innovations and solutions that help the ecosystem reach its potential and help improve the systems we use across the world
What is success for the following guiding topics?</description></item><item><title>SPO Tools and Community Projects</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/spo-tools-community-project/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/spo-tools-community-project/</guid><description>Challenge Setting
Challenge Budget: ₳1,500,000
Guiding Questions : # How can we support effective, impactful projects to build and support the SPO ecosystem and community?
Why is it important? # SPO&amp;rsquo;s play a crucial role in the Cardano ecosystem A Catalyst Challenge would incentivize the building of SPO based Projects on Cardano What is success? # Kicking off community based solutions to build SPO Tools and Platforms to offer services, events and research</description></item><item><title>Startups &amp; Onboarding for Students</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/startup-onboarding-for-students/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/challenge-setting/startup-onboarding-for-students/</guid><description>Challenge Setting
Challenge Budget: ₳100,000
Guiding Questions # How can we support student blockchain startups through Catalyst? And how can I increase the number of student Catalyst proposers and blockchain engineers?
Why? # Student entrepreneurs lack the resources needed to startup. And Cardano ecosystem also requires young Catalyst proposers and engineers.
What does success look like? # Reduce the competition rate by limiting the proposers to students. And set a budget cap and distribute opportunities to many proposers.</description></item></channel></rss>