<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sidechain Overview on</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/</link><description>Recent content in Sidechain Overview on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cardano GraphQL</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/cardano-graphql/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/cardano-graphql/</guid><description>Cardano GraphQL is cross-platform, typed, and queryable API for Cardano. It provides a query interface to all the blockchain data via GraphQL, which is a convenient choice for client applications based on web technologies (applications written in JavaScript, or any other browser-based languages, for example) that use HTTP/REST APIs to talk to other services.
For more information: Go to GitHub repo</description></item><item><title>Cardano Improvement Proposals (CIPs)</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/cips/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/cips/</guid><description>Individuals with improvement proposals for Cardano can structure those thoughts into Cardano Improvement Proposals (CIPs).
A CIP has an expected format: the proposals structure is templated to facilitate discussion and reviewing. This enables other community members to jump in and discuss specific proposals, or individual points in a proposal. The proposals and their history are also publicly available and maintained on the Cardano Foundation CIPs&amp;rsquo; Github repository.
For the non-GitHub crowd: an auto-generated companion site is being worked on at cips.</description></item><item><title>Cardano RTView</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/cardano-rtview/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/cardano-rtview/</guid><description>RTView enables developers, testers, and general users who are running nodes connected to the real cluster to see what is going on, and how the nodes are performing. It gives visibility on: how much memory and CPU is being used, the state of the blockchain, how many blocks have been forged by a particular node, how many transactions have been processed, and so on.
It is a cross-platform tool compatible with Windows, Linux, and macOS, and has a web-based user interface so you can use any browser that you want.</description></item><item><title>Cardano serialization library</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/cardano-serialization/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/cardano-serialization/</guid><description>This is a library for serialization and deserialization of data structures used in Cardano’s Haskell implementation of Shelley along with useful utility functions.
Using the library # Due to the portability of Rust, you can bind to the native Rust library from any common programming language (including C and WebAssembly). This library generates both Typescript and Flow type definitions, and you can check out possible options by just looking at Flow types.</description></item><item><title>Essential Cardano</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/essentail-cardano/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/essentail-cardano/</guid><description>Essential Cardano is an open-source community-driven Cardano library of sharable, informative content. Essential Cardano contains various types of content such as articles, videos, infographics, developer resources, weekly development updates, glossary and FAQs.
You can begin your EC experience by creating an account through the sign up button at the top right of the page, which will allow you to submit content to the hub and receive notifications about your contributions. You can contribute articles, videos and other resources for the whole Cardano community to gain from.</description></item><item><title>JSON-RPC API</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/json-rpc-api/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/json-rpc-api/</guid><description>Interacting with the sidechain requires sending requests to specific JSON-RPC API methods. The EVM sidechain testnet supports most standard Ethereum JSON-RPC API endpoints with a few exceptions described in the API specification.
Specification # The EVM sidechain testnet supports OpenRPC&amp;rsquo;s rpc.discover service discovery method that will return the OpenRPC scheme for the JSON-RPC API. You can easily validate and preview the schema on the OpenRPC Playground.
If your product requires a method that is not currently implemented, please contact Input Output Global support.</description></item><item><title>SC_Token and Test ADA</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/sidechain-token-testada/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/sidechain-token-testada/</guid><description>What is SC_Token? # SC_Token(temporary name) is the native token of the Cardano EVM sidechain Testnet. SC_Token can be moved between the main chain (Cardano) and the example EVM sidechain, and SC_Token is required to pay for gas. Test SC_Token carries no real-world value.
What is gas? # Gas refers to the computational cost necessary to successfully conduct a transaction on the sidechain network. This gas is deducted from a small fraction of SC_Token when conducting a transaction, deploying a smart contract, or writing to a smart contract.</description></item><item><title>Sidechains FAQ</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/sidechain-faq/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/sidechain-faq/</guid><description>This page answers some frequent questions for the Cardano Sidechains Toolkit and the example EVM sidechain application.
The Cardano Sidechains Toolkit # These questions relate to the components IOG provides for building custom sidechains on Cardano.
Is the Sidechain Toolkit an open-source project? # Yes, it will be open-sourced under the Input Output Global GitHub repository.
Will there be an alternative chain follower to DB Sync that consumes less resources? # Yes, IOG is working in a less resource-intensive tool.</description></item><item><title>Solidity resources</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/solidity-resource/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/solidity-resource/</guid><description>Solidity is a statically-typed curly-braces programming language designed for developing smart contracts that run on Ethereum. Because its syntax is similar to ECMAScript, it will be familiar to many developers. There are significant differences, including:
Solidity is compiled rather than interpreted It is a statically-typed language It has variadic return types. The home page # Its home is Soliditylang.org. That is the place to start if you are new to the language; if you are experienced, no doubt you will already be familiar with the site.</description></item><item><title>Transferring tokens</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/transferring-token/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-overview/transferring-token/</guid><description>This tutorial will show you how to transfer SC_Tokens between the main chain and a sidechain.
Prerequisites # We will use the sidechain-cli within this tutorial. Download the binary and add it to your shell’s path: https://github.com/input-output-hk/sidechains-tooling/releases. Download the bech32 conversion tool binary and add to your shell&amp;rsquo;s path: https://github.com/input-output-hk/bech32. If you have not done so already, create and fund your main chain and sidechain accounts: Create and fund your accounts.</description></item></channel></rss>