<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fund 9 on</title><link>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/</link><description>Recent content in Fund 9 on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title> Telegram Wallet Upgrade</title><link>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/telegramwalletupgrade/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/telegramwalletupgrade/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Telegram Wallet Upgrade # Ideascale Challenge: Dapps, Products &amp;amp; Integrations Requested Budget: 17600 The Endubis Telegram wallet requires more features in order to onboard a large audience to the Cardano community and the De-Fi world. In addition to its basic non-custodial wallet function, we will add features for cNFT displays, incorporate a P2P exchange, and integrate with Defi platforms to enable swaps, lending, and borrowing.
👉 Track the team via: # https://github.</description></item><item><title> Verify2Earn</title><link>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/verify2earn/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/verify2earn/</guid><description> Catalyst TV - Verify2Earn # Ideascale Challenge: Catalyst Natives X Cardashift: Demonstrating and monetizing impact Requested Budget: 14970 There are not enough tokenomics models which focus on advancing SDGs through tokenizing and incentivizing behavioural change. ImpactScope is designing easy-to-deploy tokenomics models which encourage and reward sustainable behaviour and impact verification.
👉 Track the team via: # https://impactscope.com https://github.com/regodo https://github.com/ImpactScope-organization</description></item><item><title>500+ ₳Community Sent to Conferences</title><link>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/500pluscommunitysenttoconferences/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/500pluscommunitysenttoconferences/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - 500+ ₳Community Sent to Conferences # As a new Cardano dApp with a lot of hustle &amp;amp; desire to grow quickly, we lack go-to-market resources to send this community to conferences and 100x user adoption &amp;amp; revenue in the next couple of months. Exhibit at major industry conferences with free tickets for the Cardano community to share the Cardano gospel, meet each other in person, and sell to decision-makers to 100x user adoption and revenue.</description></item><item><title>Accelerate Women on Cardano ECO</title><link>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/acceleratewomenoncardanoeco/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/acceleratewomenoncardanoeco/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Accelerate Women on Cardano ECO # Ideascale Challenge: Fund10 challenge setting 🌟 Women have enormous potential and can make significant contributions to the Cardano ecosystem; they should be encouraged to participate more. Therefore, Connecting and broadening the women&amp;rsquo;s knowledge as well as their roles. Significantly raise their active involvement in the Cardano ecosystem</description></item><item><title>Adacheems: Optimize the value of NFT</title><link>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/adacheems-optimizevalueofnft/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/adacheems-optimizevalueofnft/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Adacheems: Optimize the value of NFT # Ideascale Proposer: Adacheems Requested Budget: 50000 The other NFTs on the Market are too wasteful to just be on display. We bring an NFT world that includes economy, real-world connectivity, and stronger interactions for owners. AdaCheems NFT Project - Optimizing Use Values and Building the Economy of the NFT. We bring an NFT world that includes economy, real-world connectivity, and stronger interactions for owners.</description></item><item><title>Advanced Cardano NFT Search Engine</title><link>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/advancedcardanonftsearchengine/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/advancedcardanonftsearchengine/</guid><description> Catalyst TV - Advanced Cardano NFT Search Engine # Ideascale Challenge: Dapps, Products &amp;amp; Integrations Requested Budget: 56550 🌟 Cardano lacks any advanced, ecosystem-wide, NFT search and discovery tools. This makes NFT markets inefficient, limiting adoption and reducing market liquidity. Build a fast Cardano NFT search engine with faceted search functionality - enhanced by Argus’ image similarity (machine learning), and designed to accommodate future multi-chain support.
👉 Track the team via: # Argusnft Website</description></item><item><title>ATALA Prism zKP + Hyperledger Aries</title><link>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/atalaprism-zkp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/atalaprism-zkp/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - ATALA Prism zKP + Hyperledger Aries # Ideascale Challenge: Cross-Chain Collaboration Requested Budget: 82000 🌟 ATALA Prism and RootsID don&amp;rsquo;t support zero-Knowledge Proofs and Predicates and are currently not interoperable with Hyperledger Aries or W3C OBv3. Prism is only on Testnet. Let&amp;rsquo;s get ATALA on Mainnet. Build zero-Knowledge Proof and Predicate integration layer for ATALA Prism on RootsID CLI-WAL wallet and make them interoperable with Hyperledger Aries and W3C OBv3.</description></item><item><title>BEST WAY TO ATTRACT REAL GAMERS</title><link>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/bestwaytoattractrealgamers/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/bestwaytoattractrealgamers/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - BEST WAY TO ATTRACT REAL GAMERS # Ideascale Proposer: Miverse Multiverse Requested Budget: 54810 The best praise for the team is your vote, please leave a comment if you are interested!!!
Not just real gamers hate on-chained games, but we also have no sustainable, long-term way to attract - educate - convince them to try our good games. Miverse provides a comic platform and produces a comic - one of the ultimate weapons to attract real gamers on-chained.</description></item><item><title>Blockchain Course for Vietnam Devs</title><link>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/blockchaincourseforvndevs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/blockchaincourseforvndevs/</guid><description> Catalyst TV -Blockchain Course for Vietnam Devs # Ideascale Challenge: Developer Ecosystem Requested Budget: 22400 🌟 The majority of developers in Vietnam are not familiar with blockchain or are not right understand of blockchain and its importance roles to the real world. Organize short training courses for developers in Vietnam to help them have the right knowledge about blockchain technology and its application in life.
👉 Track the team via: # FIMI website FIMI Youtube Channel</description></item><item><title>Blockchain Educational dApp</title><link>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/blockchainedudapps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/vi/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund9/blockchainedudapps/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Blockchain Educational dApp # Support the Ghana team with their educational proposal This proposal seeks to develop an educational dapp on blockchain and its yields as a safe, long-term investment for the youth in Ghana. Users boarded onto the platform through community outreach, mainly across the various Ghanaian universities and beyond, will have a variety of topics to choose from, with compact yet interactive lessons to complete at their own pace</description></item></channel></rss>