<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fund 11 Info on</title><link>/docs/fund11-info/</link><description>Recent content in Fund 11 Info on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/fund11-info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Timeline</title><link>/docs/fund11-info/fund11-timeline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/fund11-info/fund11-timeline/</guid><description>Welcome to Fund11. Please check our launch guide where you can find more information about Project Catalyst and Fund categories.
Given the dynamic nature of Project Catalyst, the following dates may change as the fund progresses. If this is the case, we will notify the community via our announcement channels on Discord and Telegram.
Fund 11 Timeline # Nov 15th, 2023 · 17:00 UTC # Fund11 launches at Town Hall #146</description></item><item><title>Rules</title><link>/docs/fund11-info/fund11-rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/fund11-info/fund11-rules/</guid><description>Fund11 begins on November 15, and voting starts on January 25, and we want you to be a part of it. Below is a list of challenges alongside the amount of funding available for proposers. Proposal submissions open on November 16. The deadline for proposal submission is November 30 at 11:00 UTC. The fund will contain a total of ₳50,000,000.
Introduction # Project Catalyst is a growth engine and a grants program for the Cardano ecosystem that has funding rounds every few months, with a set amount of ada ready to allocate to ideas.</description></item><item><title>Categories</title><link>/docs/fund11-info/fund11-categories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/fund11-info/fund11-categories/</guid><description>New to Fund11, proposal submissions have been organized into new, streamlined categories and a track-based approach. Proposal categories will now fall under one of three Categories: Cardano Use cases, Cardano Open, and Catalyst Systems Improvements.
Cardano use cases # The total category budget is ₳22,500,000, divided equally into three funding tracks. Proposal submissions should answer one of the following:
Concept # Budget: ₳7,500,000
What DApp ideas or product concepts need design and prototyping to demonstrate their purpose and realize novel applications or use cases of the Cardano blockchain?</description></item><item><title>Catalyst network</title><link>/docs/fund11-info/catalyst-network/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/fund11-info/catalyst-network/</guid><description>What is the Catalyst Network? # The Catalyst network formerly known as Coordinator is a collective of projects from all rounds of funding.
Catalyst provides an innovative environment where the community can explore the highest potential of human collaboration, and the Catalyst Network is one of those spaces that allow funded projects to network, collaborate, explore topics, and even gain new insights and perspectives from leaders within and outside the Cardano community.</description></item></channel></rss>