<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Proposer Guidance on</title><link>/docs/catalyst-guide/</link><description>Recent content in Proposer Guidance on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/catalyst-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Proposal submission Guide</title><link>/docs/catalyst-guide/proposal-submission-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/catalyst-guide/proposal-submission-guide/</guid><description>This page guides proposers in submitting their proposal in ideascale
There are many resources available to help you navigate the proposal submission process.
For additional assistance, please consider reviewing the following documents and support:
Key dates:
Deadline to submit draft proposals - November 30, 2023 at 11:00 AM UTC
Deadline to finalise proposals - December 7, 2023 at 11:00 AM UTC
Note: Any largely blank proposals (empty drafts with many TBD/TBC/coming soon items) or ideas with titles such as &amp;ldquo;Placeholder&amp;rdquo; may be archived without notice at any time.</description></item><item><title>Scoring guidance for the Proposer</title><link>/docs/catalyst-guide/submit-a-proposal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/catalyst-guide/submit-a-proposal/</guid><description>This page provides an overview of what Community Reviewers will consider when submitting their opinions
Community Reviewers will score each proposal between 1-5 for each of the three criteria listed below. They are asked to opine on whether the proposal has clearly outlined its ability to provide a solution within the context of the three criteria:
IMPACT CAPABILITY &amp;amp; FEASIBILITY VALUE FOR MONEY PLEASE NOTE: Do not assume that every Community Reviewer has technical or subject matter expertise.</description></item><item><title>Challenge and Proposal Guide</title><link>/docs/catalyst-guide/guides/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/catalyst-guide/guides/</guid><description>Project Catalyst is underway and we’re seeing some incredible participation from a wide spectrum of individuals. This is a collaborative process to create a worldwide community innovation project. The problem statement, solution, relevant experience, and funds requested will be displayed in the voting application. This will allow everyone to learn about the initiatives before voting on them.
The proposal plans and attachments can be viewed on our innovation platform, hosted by Ideascale, in order to gain an understanding of the details.</description></item><item><title>Additional Guidance</title><link>/docs/catalyst-guide/additional-guild/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/catalyst-guide/additional-guild/</guid><description>Open Source Guidance # Open source refers to something people can modify and share because its design is publicly accessible. Open-source software has source code that anyone can inspect, modify, and enhance. Open-source software, hardware, and data solutions encourage greater transparency and security and help reduce costs by developing, collaborating, and fixing in the open. It helps create developer-friendly tooling and approaches that streamline an integrated development environment, helping to develop code more efficiently and providing ease of use for developers.</description></item></channel></rss>