<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on</title><link>/docs/12docs/overview/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/12docs/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Be Part of the Governance</title><link>/docs/12docs/overview/be-part-of-the-governance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/overview/be-part-of-the-governance/</guid><description>Cardano was designed with the intent of long-term sustainability in mind. The goal was to build a system that could govern and fund itself without relying on donations. Cardano includes a built-in treasury system that receives revenue via transaction fees and treasury taxes on a regular basis. This is explained in detail in treasuries with Bingsheng Zhang.
Cardano Improvement Proposal # Cardano Improvement Proposals (CIPs) are a way of formally proposing ideas in an agreed-upon fashion.</description></item><item><title>Cardano architecture</title><link>/docs/12docs/overview/cardano-architecture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/overview/cardano-architecture/</guid><description>This section describes the high-level architecture of Cardano. It provides details on the core components and their interactions, and briefly discusses Cardano&amp;rsquo;s eras and implementations.
High level architecture of Cardano # The following diagram outlines the interaction between the system components of Cardano:
System components # The current implementation of Cardano is highly modular. It includes the following components (different deployment use cases will use different combinations of components):
Node Command line interface (CLI) Daedalus wallet Cardano db-sync GraphQL API server (Apollo) SMASH server Nodes and remote nodes # A blockchain system consists of a set of nodes distributed across a network that communicate with each other to achieve consensus about the system’s state.</description></item><item><title>Cardano nodes</title><link>/docs/12docs/overview/cardano-nodes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/overview/cardano-nodes/</guid><description>The Cardano node is the top-level component within the network. Network nodes connect to each other within the networking layer, which is the driving force for delivering information exchange requirements. This includes new block diffusion and transaction information for establishing a better data flow. Cardano nodes maintain connections with peers that have been chosen via a custom peer-selection process. By running a Cardano node, you are participating in and contributing to the network.</description></item><item><title>Cardano tracking tools</title><link>/docs/12docs/overview/cardano-tracking-tools/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/overview/cardano-tracking-tools/</guid><description>Since Cardano is a public blockchain ledger, it is possible to easily track all recent transactions, block details, and epoch data using different tools.
Exploring transactions and blocks # Cardano Explorer
Cardano Explorer is a user-oriented tool that fetches data from the main database and reflects it in a straightforward and convenient web interface.
The Explorer shows the latest epoch details. You can click the latest epoch and see:
a number of blocks produced during this epoch time the epoch started time of last produced block number of processed transactions total output in ada Figure 1.</description></item><item><title>How to delegate and earn rewards?</title><link>/docs/12docs/overview/how-to-delegate-and-earn-reward/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/overview/how-to-delegate-and-earn-reward/</guid><description>Ada that is held on Cardano represents its holder’s stake in the protocol. The size of the stake is proportional to the amount of ada held. Users who hold a stake in Cardano can earn passive rewards for validating blocks.
Since not everyone has the time, knowledge, or resources to run a stake pool, ada holders can delegate their stake to a preferred pool and let an operator maintain their stake on their behalf.</description></item><item><title>How to purchase ada?</title><link>/docs/12docs/overview/how-to-purchase-ada/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/overview/how-to-purchase-ada/</guid><description>Note: we are not making any investment advice. Please consider conducting your own research and due diligence, or consult your financial advisor before making any investment decisions.
Like any other cryptocurrency, ada can be purchased using one of the available exchanges.
We do not recommend any particular exchange, as there are many great options. However, you can find a list of exchanges listing ada on Cardano markets.
Step 1 Download a wallet # First, you need to download and install a cryptocurrency wallet that supports ada.</description></item><item><title>Learn about Plutus</title><link>/docs/12docs/overview/learn-about-plutus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/overview/learn-about-plutus/</guid><description>Plutus is the native smart contract language for Cardano. It is a Turing-complete language written in Haskell, and Plutus smart contracts are effectively Haskell programs. By using Plutus, you can be confident in the correct execution of your smart contracts. It draws from modern language research to provide a safe, full-stack programming environment based on Haskell, the leading purely-functional programming language.
The Alonzo upgrade brings exciting and highly anticipated capabilities to Cardano through the integration of Plutus scripts onto the blockchain.</description></item><item><title>Proof of stake</title><link>/docs/12docs/overview/proof-of-stake/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/overview/proof-of-stake/</guid><description>Proof of stake (PoS) is a type of consensus mechanism or protocol that uses the amount of stake (or value) held in the system to determine consensus. In essence, a consensus protocol is what controls the laws and parameters governing the behavior of blockchains. Think of consensus as a ruleset that each network participant adheres to. As blockchains are not controlled by any single, central authority, a consensus protocol is used instead to allow distributed network participants to agree on the history of the network captured on the blockchain – to reach consensus on what has happened, and continue from a single source of truth.</description></item><item><title>Types of wallets</title><link>/docs/12docs/overview/type-of-wallets/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/overview/type-of-wallets/</guid><description>A cryptocurrency wallet is a safe and secure place where users can keep their digital currencies.
Remember, only a wallet that you have private keys to (a password that provides access to your cryptocurrency) is considered to be safe to store your personal funds. It is highly not recommended to store cryptocurrency on exchanges, as this increases the risk of funds loss.
Not your keys, not your coins ‒ they say.</description></item><item><title>What is a cryptocurrency?</title><link>/docs/12docs/overview/whatiscryptocurrency/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/overview/whatiscryptocurrency/</guid><description>A cryptocurrency is a digital asset, which is stored on the ledger and is designed to serve as a medium of exchange for goods or services. It is otherwise called crypto.
Blockchain ledgers serve as the underlying technology for cryptocurrency creation in a decentralized environment. Blockchain protocols use rigorous cryptography techniques to enable the minting (creation) of cryptocurrency and to secure and verify crypto ownership and fund movement records. The price of cryptocurrency is not controlled by a government or centralized financial institution.</description></item></channel></rss>