<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Guests Guidelines on</title><link>/ja/guest/guest-info/</link><description>Recent content in Guests Guidelines on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/ja/guest/guest-info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intro</title><link>/ja/guest/guest-info/guest-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ja/guest/guest-info/guest-guidelines/</guid><description>Notes:
Some contents and information used in this page has been re-used and/or replicated from Catalyst Swam ATH Host Guides v2
Purposes # A bi-weekly Eastern Town Hall (ETH) meetup is a place for Eastern Hemisphere communities to update, share ideas, present projects, invite the community into meaningful discussions, and find like-minded people to collaborate and build projects together on the Cardano blockchain.
Hosting a Breakout room for your own community, and events to support Project Catalyst goals, we wish to provide a safe and lively environment to explore the highest potential of human collaboration as well as to onboard, introduce and educate community members to our ecosystem.</description></item><item><title>Sign-up form</title><link>/ja/guest/guest-info/guest-signup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ja/guest/guest-info/guest-signup/</guid><description>Sign-up through the following link: Breakout room registration Sign up to the form above. Once the hosting session is accepted, your room and room title/topic will be announced at the end of the Town Hall to the community and a short description will appear on &amp;lt;https://easterntownhall.com/guests/actual name_here&amp;gt; Check for our announcement in the Project Catalyst Announcement Telegram a couple of hours before the Town Hall for confirmation of your Breakout Room.</description></item><item><title>FAQs</title><link>/ja/guest/guest-info/guest-faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ja/guest/guest-info/guest-faq/</guid><description>📍 Do I need to register to host a Breakout room? # Yes, please fill in the following form.
📍 How do we accept your Breakout room register? # You need to fill in the form provided and allow us at least 1 week for ETH Core Team members to validate provided info and once the consensus result of being accepted/rejected from the ETH team, you will be notified of the outcome.</description></item><item><title>Presentation</title><link>/ja/guest/guest-info/guest-presentation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ja/guest/guest-info/guest-presentation/</guid><description>Be punctual: Town Hall starts at 9.00 UTC and as co-host on that day, you need to join registered Zoom from at the following link: Zoom link to register to the ETH at least 10 mins before 9:00 UTC to finalize the preparations for your presentation. Recording: To be able to record your Breakout room onto your computer, we will assign you as a co-host before the rooms open. Important: As co-host, you are able to close your room when your session is done, but you are also able to close all breakout rooms.</description></item><item><title>Upload recording</title><link>/ja/guest/guest-info/guest-upload-recording/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ja/guest/guest-info/guest-upload-recording/</guid><description>
Please share the recording within 5 days post-recording. Please feel free to upload recordings to your own channel, but at the ETH we upload recordings to our ETH Youtube Account to allow everyone to catch up on great discussions, sessions, and workshops. Then please send an email with a title and description for your recording to easterntownhall@gmail.com.</description></item></channel></rss>