<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Challenges fund 6 on</title><link>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/</link><description>Recent content in Challenges fund 6 on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/catalyst/fund6/challenges/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Atala PRISM DID Mass-Scale Adoption</title><link>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/atala-prism-did/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/atala-prism-did/campaign-brief/</guid><description>What will drive mass-scale adoption of decentralized IDs on Cardano?
Fund Size: $250,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Campaign Brief # Propose a means or way to drive mass-scale adoption of DID usage as an easy-to-use onramp to the Cardano ecosystem (preferably Atala PRISM when released). This can include any method that will offer users or entities a decentralized ID to start defining their digital self-sovereignty. Think about how this is implemented at scale drawing millions of users, who, once onboard, can become customers for dApps, tools, DeFi and other services.</description></item><item><title>Cardano Emerging Threat Alarm</title><link>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/emerging-threats/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/emerging-threats/campaign-brief/</guid><description>How can we help stakeholders identify serious emerging systemic threats for the Cardano blockchain before a threat overcomes the system?
Fund Size: $50,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Campaign Brief # Blockchain systems are a complex amalgam of technological, economic and social components that rely and are used by many stakeholders from different geographies and backgrounds. These systems are not isolated from the real world and unexpected threats may emerge from the dynamic interaction.</description></item><item><title>Catalyst value onboarding</title><link>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/catalyst-value-onboarding/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/catalyst-value-onboarding/campaign-brief/</guid><description>How can we encourage meaningful participation in Project Catalyst from community members in the next two funds?
Fund Size: $75,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Campaign Brief # The growth of Cardano depends on meaningful participation from proposers, advisors, and voters.
How success looks like # There&amp;rsquo;s a strong funnel to motivate, inform and direct new participants towards providing a contribution that improves Catalyst&amp;rsquo;s ROI.
Key metric to measure # To assess ROI of this challenge we will ask ourselves:</description></item><item><title>DApps &amp; Integrations</title><link>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/dapps-integrations/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/dapps-integrations/campaign-brief/</guid><description>What applications will provide the most value for end users in 2021?
Fund Size: $250,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Campaign Brief # Quality Dapps and integrations will increase utility &amp;amp; adoption of Cardano.
How success looks like # Novel and viable applications get built of top of Cardano attracting users. Integrations manage to pull in more adoption.
Key metric to measure # To assess the challenge we will be asking ourselves: Did our efforts manage to attract users to the platform?</description></item><item><title>DeFi and Microlending for Africa</title><link>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/defi-microlending/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/defi-microlending/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $90,000 USD paid in Ada
How can we enable the creation of micro-lending and Defi dApp solutions that fits the African setting?
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Why is it important? # Microlending and DeFi dApps targeted specifically to the African context &amp;amp; based on historical cultural norms will accelerate user adoption
How does success look like? # Businesses are confident to submit well-researched proposals that address the African micro-lending and decentralized finance context</description></item><item><title>Developer ecosystem</title><link>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/developer-ecosystem/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/developer-ecosystem/campaign-brief/</guid><description>How can we create a positive developer experience that helps the developer focus on building successful apps?
Fund Size: $1,005,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Campaign Brief # Creating an awesome experience that incentives developers, will lead to increased developer adoption, productivity, and creativity.
How success looks like # Liveliness. Happy energized developers making money and achieving their goals, mutual help, collaboration, and a shared feeling of success.</description></item><item><title>Disaster: When all is at stake</title><link>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/disaster/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/disaster/campaign-brief/</guid><description>How can we help SPOs tackle risks &amp;amp; plan, develop and participate in disaster recovery tests in a safe hiccup-free and decentralized manner?
Fund Size: $150,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Campaign Brief # Disaster recovery (DR) is an area of security planning that aims to protect an organization from the effects of significant negative events.
Having a disaster recovery strategy in place enables an organization to maintain or quickly resume mission-critical functions following a disruption.</description></item><item><title>Distributed decision making</title><link>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/distributed-decision/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/distributed-decision/campaign-brief/</guid><description>How can we help the Catalyst community to get better at distributed decision making within the next two Catalyst rounds?
Fund Size: $75,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Campaign Brief # High-quality and decentralized decision-making, will increase treasury ROI and legitimize decentralized governance.
How success looks like # The community is consciously improving decision-making processes while growing a group of committed and collaborative leaders.
Key metrics to measure # To assess ROI of this challenge we will ask ourselves: Did we get better at distributed decision making?</description></item><item><title>DLT Entrepreneurship Toolbox</title><link>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/dlt-enterpreneurship/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/dlt-enterpreneurship/campaign-brief/</guid><description>How can early stage entrepreneurs develop their skills to execute &amp;amp; communicate great ideas so voters/stakeholders value the project?
Fund Size: $150,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Campaign Brief # Whatever your background, confidently communicating all the important elements of an early stage venture can be overwhelming for inexperienced entrepreneurs.
More should be done to help an increasingly diverse group of Project Catalyst entrepreneurs, at different stages of self-development, plus their teams and stakeholders to collaborate and communicate effectively.</description></item><item><title>Fund 7 Challenge Setting</title><link>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/fund7-challenge-setting/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund6/challenges/fund7-challenge-setting/campaign-brief/</guid><description>What Challenges should the community prioritize to address in Fund7?
Fund Size: $5,400,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Campaign Brief # Community defined challenges are critical for Cardano community self-governance, and generate a unique way to achieve Cardano&amp;rsquo;s mission.
Challenge setting is different from other challenges as it&amp;rsquo;s about proposing new challenges, whether regular challenges are about proposing initiatives to address challenges.
Once a proposal is accepted by the community, the proposing team has an opportunity to receive a &amp;ldquo;Challenge team&amp;rdquo; incentive of $2,500 worth of ada, if the following conditions are met:</description></item></channel></rss>