<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sidechain Essentials on</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/</link><description>Recent content in Sidechain Essentials on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About block explorer</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/block-explorer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/block-explorer/</guid><description>A block explorer allows you to inspect a blockchain to see its blocks and transactions.
This document is based primarily on the Blockscout explorer, but blockchain explorers necessarily use similar terminology and follow a similar pattern in their presentation of information.
When you use a block explorer, it will list fields and their contents. This document will help you understand the meaning of the field names and the significance of their contents.</description></item><item><title>About Ouroboros BFT</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/about-ouroboros/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/about-ouroboros/</guid><description>Ouroboros BFT: A simple Byzantine fault tolerant consensus protocol # Ouroboros, named after the symbol of infinity, is the backbone of the Cardano ecosystem. Ouroboros BFT is the version that is implemented in Cardano&amp;rsquo;s example EVM sidechain. It is a simple, deterministic protocol for ledger consensus that tolerates Byzantine faults.
Background # So what is a Byzantine fault? To understand that, we have to go back to 1982, to the Byzantine generals problem paper by Leslie Lamport, Robert Shostak, and Marshall Pease.</description></item><item><title>Chain follower</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/chain-follower/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/chain-follower/</guid><description>A chain follower such as DB Sync is a component that observes the transactions on the main chain such as Cardano. The chain follower provides the information for a sidechain to stay consistent with the main chain.
The DB Sync page gives detailed information about the functionality and how to set it up.
Using the chain follower on a sidechain # The sidechain node uses DB Sync for getting information regarding the main chain.</description></item><item><title>Committee rotation</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/committee-rotation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/committee-rotation/</guid><description>A sidechain is initialized by an SPO, or &amp;lsquo;chain creator&amp;rsquo; who publishes the sidechain Plutus contract implementations including committee registration scripts. These registration scripts allow other SPOs to register or de-register as a candidate in the committee. The SPO also runs a sidechain validator node which starts the sidechain when a quorum of validators is reached.
The sidechain is validated by an SPO committee where each SPO is a candidate running a sidechain validator node.</description></item><item><title>Create and fund accounts</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/create-fund-acc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/create-fund-acc/</guid><description>Prerequisites: # Ability to make an HTTP request. How to fund your main chain account with test ada tokens # In this tutorial, you will learn how to claim test ada tokens on the main chain testnet (to pay for main chain transaction fees).
Note: This is a dedicated Cardano testnet separate from the preview and pre-production testing environments.
Generating keys # To generate keys for the Cardano testnet you need the cardano-cli binary.</description></item><item><title>Introduction to sidechains</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/intro/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/intro/</guid><description>A sidechain is simply a blockchain that depends on its main chain and is connected to it. This configuration allows the sidechain to have its own consensus algorithm and features. The sidechain is connected to the main chain through a two-way peg that allows the moving of assets between the chains. The finality of blocks is determined through a consensus mechanism that relies on the security of the main chain.</description></item><item><title>Main chain Plutus scripts</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/plutus-scripts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/plutus-scripts/</guid><description>The main chain utilizes the following components to handle interactions with a sidechain:
SidechainTokenMintingPolicy: a minting policy that validates the minting or burning of sidechain tokens (SC_Token) on the main chain. MPTRootTokenMintingPolicy: a minting policy for storing cross-chain transaction bundles&amp;rsquo; MPT roots. CommitteeCandidateValidator: a script address for committee candidates. MPTRootTokenValidator: a script address for storing MPTRootTokens. CommitteeHashValidator: a script address for the committee members&amp;rsquo; hash. All of these policies and validators are parameterized by the sidechain parameters, which allows getting unique minting policy and validator script hashes.</description></item><item><title>Network details</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/network-detail/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/network-detail/</guid><description>The Example EVM sidechain testnet environment consists of two networks:
EVM sidechain testnet (sidechain, SC) A dedicated Cardano testnet (main chain, MN) Networks # Name Network Type Chain ID Consensus Token Model EVM sidechain testnet Testnet 78 OBFT Sidechain token (SC_Token) Account model Cardano testnet Testnet 7 POS Test ada EUTXO Network utilities # Example EVM Sidechain # RPC https://faucet.sidechain.evmtestnet.iohkdev.io/ (same url as faucet) Block Explorer https://explorer.sidechain.evmtestnet.iohkdev.io/ Faucet https://faucet.sidechain.evmtestnet.iohkdev.io/ Dedicated Cardano Testnet # Faucet https://faucet.</description></item><item><title>Set up development environment</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/setup-dev-env/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/setup-dev-env/</guid><description>The EVM sidechain testnet is EVM-compatible with most Ethereum software to develop and deploy smart contracts including:
Remix Hardhat Truffle Remix # This tutorial will show you how to deploy a Solidity smart contract to the EVM sidechain testnet using Remix. Remix is an online IDE to develop and deploy Solidity smart contracts.
Prerequisites # In this tutorial, you will use MetaMask as your wallet and Web3 provider. If you have not done so already, create or import an account with MetaMask and fund your wallet with testnet tokens using the faucet.</description></item><item><title>Sidechain Toolkit Introduction</title><link>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/toolkit-into/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/12docs/sidechain-essentials/toolkit-into/</guid><description>The Sidechain Toolkit is a set of components and recommendations to extend Cardano. The toolkit allows blockchain developers to deploy customizable solutions that fit their technical and social needs. The toolkit is composed of three main components:
Main-chain Plutus scripts # Plutus scripts deployed on the Cardano main chain define the flow of a particular sidechain. These scripts are the beginning of the initialization of a sidechain containing Plutus scripts for block producer candidate registrations, minting policies of the sidechain’s token, and moving tokens functions.</description></item></channel></rss>