<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IdeaFest on</title><link>/catalyst/fund11/idea-fest/</link><description>Recent content in IdeaFest on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/catalyst/fund11/idea-fest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>27/01/2024</title><link>/catalyst/fund11/idea-fest/27-01-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund11/idea-fest/27-01-2024/</guid><description>1. Token Engineering on Cardano: Modelling &amp;amp; simulation of token economic systems # Presenter: Yohann Irani Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides: N/A Proposal summary: Tokens are more than digital money, they&amp;rsquo;re foundational to digital economic systems. Pre-coding, token models should be modelled &amp;amp; analysed. That requires an engineering discipline &amp;amp; supporting tools. 2. Online Training Platform for Talents and Freelancers on Cardano - PRO39 # Presenter: Ha Nguyen Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: Establish a value-for-money, hands-on, flexible online learning platform so that talents and freelancers can quickly gain knowledge and apply it to their relevant job requirements.</description></item><item><title>20/01/2024</title><link>/catalyst/fund11/idea-fest/20-01-2024/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund11/idea-fest/20-01-2024/</guid><description>1. dReps Onboarding: Empowering Cardano Ghana Community # Presenter: Seidu Ziblim Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: To organise four (4) regional events to educate, develop and onboard 200 people with diverse backgrounds with the Skills of Voting, dReps and vote delegation to dRep through educational events. 2. dApp Web3 Freelancer Service Marketplace on Cardano - PRO39 # Presenter: Ha Nguyen Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: Establish a dApp Web3 Service marketplace to offer affordable Blockchain services, connecting project owners and freelancers, thereby accelerating the growth of Catalyst and Blockchain startups.</description></item></channel></rss>