<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>IdeaFest on</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/</link><description>Recent content in IdeaFest on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>26/08/2023</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/26-08-2023/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/26-08-2023/</guid><description>1. dRep TV Hub - to connect 100 dReps &amp;lt;=&amp;gt; thousands of Voters (available in English, Japanese and Vietnamese) # Presenter: Mie Tran Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: We will create an official Youtube channel to introduce dRep to Voters and PR in the community. We will interview in main language and translate subtitles into Japanese, Vietnamese, and English. 2. Socious: Extended Quadratic Funding for Open Source Projects # Presenter: Seira Yun Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: Current crowdfunding platforms favor the wealthy, neglecting diversity and fairness, hindering underrepresented open-source projects.</description></item><item><title>19/08/2023</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/19-08-2023/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/19-08-2023/</guid><description>1. Vcoincheck quizz - Quizz and earn everything!!! # Presenter: Ilum Nguyen Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: We will create quizzes for all levels of blockchain and Cardano knowledge. Community can do quizzes and learn knowledge through our websites. Quizzes and knowledge are made by Cardano enthusiants 2. Cardano Asia TikTok Channel (Expand to Japan 🇯🇵 and Vietnam 🇻🇳) # Presenter: Mr. Buck Nguyen Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: Keeping Fund 9 promise, the Cardano TikTok channel gained 100k+ followers/interactions since the launch.</description></item><item><title>12/08/2023</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/12-08-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/12-08-2023/</guid><description>1. Andamio by Gimbalabs: a learning management system (LMS) built on Cardano with skill-tracking, treasury management, and smart contract capabilities # Presenter: Roberto Mayen-Hess Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: Andamio: A unique Cardano innovation, blending PBL-based LMS with treasury management. Streamlined onboarding for orgs and seamless learning-to-project transition. Simplify contributor onboarding with our business solution and gain project-related skills. 2. [C2VN]: Researching and manufacturing handheld real-time LAMP prototypes with IoT and Blockchain integration for rapid disease analysis # Presenter: Ngoc Huynh Van Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: Development of a Point-of-Care Real-time LAMP prototyping with IoT and Blockchain integration enables real-time management and statistical analysis of infections, making it easy to track infections 3.</description></item><item><title>05/08/2023</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/05-08-2023/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/05-08-2023/</guid><description>1. SPO Campaign in Communities # Presenter: Ivan Kwananda Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: We want to host six monthly campaigns about SPO in Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s blockchain communities. We will teach them about how to be SPO in Cardano and also encourage them to stake their ADA in SPO to support decentralization and the Cardano ecosystem. 2. Sisu Network Bridge: A secure and user-friendly bridge for seamless cross-chain asset transfers on Cardano # Presenter: Steven Nguyen Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: We&amp;rsquo;ll integrate Sisu Network to Cardano Enabling seamless communication &amp;amp; asset transfers across blockchains Enhancing interoperability, liquidity &amp;amp; user experience Scalable, secure &amp;amp; developer-friendly 3.</description></item><item><title>29/07/2023</title><link>/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/29-07-2023/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund10/idea-fest/29-07-2023/</guid><description>🇮🇩 Indonesia - IdeaFest Reel Sessions # 1. SPO Campaign in Communities # Presenter: Ivan Kwananda Ideascale URL Youtube URL Presentation slides Proposal summary: We want to host six monthly campaigns about SPO in Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s blockchain communities. We will teach them about how to be SPO in Cardano and also encourage them to stake their ADA in SPO to support decentralization and the Cardano ecosystem. 🇯🇵 Japan - IdeaFest Reel Sessions # 1.</description></item></channel></rss>