<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Challenges fund 9 on</title><link>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/</link><description>Recent content in Challenges fund 9 on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Building on Blockfrost</title><link>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/building-on-blockfrost/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/building-on-blockfrost/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: 50,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page
Challenge Brief # Blockfrost is an instant, public and freely accessible API that removes infrastructure obstacles for developers so that everyone can start building (d)apps on Cardano. With Blockfrost, developers can start doing what they love ❤️, without the need for running and maintaining additional infrastructure and tooling themselves. At the moment, we have more than 10,000 developers already onboarded in our Blockfrost.</description></item><item><title>Challenge &amp; Scouted for Students 🎓</title><link>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/challenge-scouted-for-students/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/challenge-scouted-for-students/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: 100,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page
Challenge Brief # Student entrepreneurs have exciting business ideas and motivations to start a business, but they lack the resources to implement them. In particular, the shortage of development funds and engineers is serious, and students have few opportunities to get these resources. However, Catalysts are easier to raise money than VCs(Venture Capital) and Business Contests, and also can connect globally with engineers in this community.</description></item><item><title>Cross-Chain Collaboration</title><link>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/cross-chain-collaboration/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/cross-chain-collaboration/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: 900,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page
Challenge Brief # Background # Why is this Challenge needed?
Tribalism &amp;amp; maximalism are harmful. We are in the multi-chain future. Interoperability is the key. We need initiatives to increase communication, coordination and collaboration between chains. We have common challenges. Let’s solve those together. Common challenges for all blockchain communities # You could buddy up with someone from outside Cardano ecosystem and address one or more of these common challenges:</description></item><item><title>DAOs ❤ Cardano</title><link>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/daos-love-cardano/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/daos-love-cardano/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $1,000,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page
Challenge Brief # Currently if a DAO (even one that is aimed to build products and services around Cardano) wants to setup their DAO infrastructure, the current options are all based on, mostly, the Ethereum blockchain.
These dApps range from basic Treasury management, to Decision making in DAOs and even supporting services like Decentralized Justice. Some of them are:
https://aragon.org https://daostack.</description></item><item><title>Dapps,Products &amp; Integrations</title><link>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/dapps-products-integrations/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/dapps-products-integrations/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: 7,850,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page
Challenge Brief # Dapps, Products &amp;amp; Integrations is focused on the following areas:
Creation or improvement of different Dapps, products, and integrations that provide value to the Cardano community and wider ecosystem. Integrations with other existing services, products, and protocols that improve the end-user experience whether that&amp;rsquo;s giving the user more options or making something easier to use that benefits the wider ecosystem.</description></item><item><title>Develper Ecosystem</title><link>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/developer-ecosystem/campagin-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/developer-ecosystem/campagin-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: 1,000,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page
Challenge Brief # Without the supportive environment for developers, new innovations would be stalled. By supporting this challenge settings, more developers would be drawn into Cardano. There would be a bigger talent pool of developers that Catalyst projects can collaborate with and turn project concepts/Proof of concept into successful protocols which would enhance the growth of Cardano.
Guiding Questions # What are the the tools that we need to prioritize first How do we attract developers from outside of our current community to participate in Catalyst?</description></item><item><title>dRep improvement and onboarding</title><link>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/drep-improvement-onboarding/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/drep-improvement-onboarding/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: 150,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page
Challenge Brief # The dRep could not be more important to Cardano given the following
The participation rate of Catalyst voting is less than 20%. Statistics show that 30% of Catalyst voters randomly vote without reading the proposals. It is difficult for Catalyst users who are not necessarily skilled in technology and English to judge nearly 1,000 proposals. Potential relevance to Decentralized Consortium Funding and roadmap approval voting through 2025.</description></item><item><title>Grow Africa, Grow Cardano</title><link>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/grow-africa-grow-cardano/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/grow-africa-grow-cardano/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: 500,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page
Challenge Brief # It&amp;rsquo;s no secret that Cardano is recognized as a blockchain with a strong focus on Africa, and formally stated as such in Cardano&amp;rsquo;s strategic goals. However, as other blockchain protocols recognize the potential of crypto in Africa, without concrete sustained action, Cardano risks losing a potential $1 trillion in market share of the African market to other blockchains within the next 3 years.</description></item><item><title>Grow East Asia, Grow Cardano</title><link>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/grow-east-asia-grow-cardano/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/grow-east-asia-grow-cardano/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: 250,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page
Challenge Brief # As in Africa, raising the awareness levels of regular people in East Asia about blockchain and the Cardano network should be a priority for the Catalyst community. In this challenge, we provide funding for people who have learned about Cardano to take advantage of the community&amp;rsquo;s support and build on or use the Cardano network.
The nature of the proposals for this challenge is open-ended.</description></item><item><title>legal &amp; financial implementation</title><link>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/legal-and-finacial-implementation/campagin-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/catalyst/fund9/challenges/legal-and-finacial-implementation/campagin-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: 500,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page
Challenge Brief # Currently the real Challenge for Funded proposals relies on implementing legal and financial boundaries and frameworks for their projects.
Providing funded proposals with solutions and services to operate legally in their residing country will open new possibilities and provide peace of mind to the project owners.
Many projects will broaden their horizons and increase their impact on the Ecosystem once legal and financial frameworks are explored and established.</description></item></channel></rss>