<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Community Reviewers on</title><link>/docs/community-advisers/</link><description>Recent content in Community Reviewers on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/docs/community-advisers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to become a Community Reviewer?</title><link>/docs/community-advisers/become-a-ca/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/community-advisers/become-a-ca/</guid><description>As a Community Reviewer (previously referred to as Proposal Assessor) you play an important role in the Catalyst funding process by providing your opinion as an input to voters who may use your feedback about a proposal to help make their decisions whether to vote for the proposal or not.
Community reviewers could be fairly new to the Cardano ecosystem or they could be veterans that have been involved with Cardano and Catalyst for a long time.</description></item><item><title>Levels and Rewards</title><link>/docs/community-advisers/ca-level/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/community-advisers/ca-level/</guid><description>How do I progress through the Community Reviewer levels? # For Fund10 # For each previously held Proposal Assessor (PA) ID, based on the past performance of old funds, the relative percentage of valid assessments submitted that were either Excellent OR Good, is a qualifying factor to determine a LV0, LV1, or LV2 Community Review level. This parameter allows setting a minimum % of valid assessments to qualify previously held PA IDs in Fund10.</description></item><item><title>LV0 and LV1 - Scoring Rubric &amp; Guiding Questions</title><link>/docs/community-advisers/ca-scoring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/community-advisers/ca-scoring/</guid><description>For each of the three criteria, Community Reviewers are required to give their opinion and rationale in English to explain the score and demonstrate the assessor’s critical thinking. A proposal may receive a low score for various reasons, including if the funding application form is not complete, the applicant cannot be clearly identified, or if the project does not comply with Fund 10 Rules. If a rationale does not correspond with the score given, the review will likely be filtered out in the Moderation Stage.</description></item><item><title>Community Moderation Process</title><link>/docs/community-advisers/community-mod/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/community-advisers/community-mod/</guid><description>All reviews the Community Reviewers provide will be subject to an automated review process using Catalyst Flags. Catalyst Flags* are pieces of code known as scripts that are run to analyze all reviews by the Community Reviewers. Catalyst scripts will raise flags in case of;
Similarity ~ reviews which are identical or almost identical to a previously submitted review Profanity ~ reviews that contain profanities or abusive content or language Use of AI ~ reviews that do not reflect the opinion of the Community Reviewer or which are provided by others or an AI-agent acting on their behalf.</description></item><item><title>Rules to be followed by Community Moderators (LV2)</title><link>/docs/community-advisers/rules-for-ca-lv2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/community-advisers/rules-for-ca-lv2/</guid><description>All reviews should be provided to voters if a Community Moderator has good reason not to include it. Community Moderators are anticipated to approve many flagged reviews and will be retained for voters to consider. Moderators are there to provide a sanity check to verify if the flag(s) have raised a valid concern. Moderators should use their best judgment and give a reason if they agree the flag is valid, meaning the review should not be included.</description></item></channel></rss>