<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Kontribusi on</title><link>/id/docs/contribution/</link><description>Recent content in Kontribusi on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/id/docs/contribution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>c3eth Contribution Guidelines</title><link>/id/docs/contribution/c3eth-contribute/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/docs/contribution/c3eth-contribute/</guid><description>We use Hugo to format and generate the c3eth website and the Doks theme for styling and site structure.
Doks is a Hugo theme for building secure, fast, and SEO-ready documentation websites, which you can easily update and customize.
All submissions, including submissions by project members, require review. We use GitHub pull requests for this purpose. Consult GitHub Help for more information on using pull requests.
Updating a single page # If you&amp;rsquo;ve just spotted something you&amp;rsquo;d like to change while using the docs, Doks has a shortcut for you:</description></item><item><title>Pelokalan Dokumen C3ETH</title><link>/id/docs/contribution/translation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/id/docs/contribution/translation/</guid><description>Terima kasih atas minat Anda untuk menerjemahkan (melokalkan) Dokumen C3ETH 😊 Pekerjaan Anda membuat dokumen lebih mudah diakses dan tersedia lebih luas untuk komunitas kami di seluruh dunia.
👉 Silakan ikuti panduan di bawah ini untuk membantu menerjemahkan Dokumen C3ETH.
Langkah-langkah untuk berpartisipasi dalam menerjemahkan dokumen C3ETH: # Buka file GITLOCALIZATION_CONTRIBUTORS . Cari header bahasa yang ingin Anda kontribusikan dan tambahkan nama lengkap dan @your_github_account Anda di bawah header. Jika Anda tidak dapat menemukan bahasa yang ingin Anda sumbangkan, harap baca bagian ini .</description></item></channel></rss>