<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Fund 8 on</title><link>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/</link><description>Recent content in Fund 8 on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cardano Annual Market Report</title><link>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/cardanoannualmarketreport/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/cardanoannualmarketreport/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Cardano Annual Market Report # Make a market report with professional methodology, implement results in multi-channel communication, especially publish in local mediums. Shout out to one of the well-prepared proposals in Fund8 of Mr. Tung Tran planning to build a creditable database report
Challenge: F8: Film + Media (FAM) creatives unite! Proposal: Cardano Annual Market Report Requested Fund: 10000 Meet the Team: # Tran Thanh Tung</description></item><item><title>Cardano Coffee lounge in Vietnam</title><link>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/cardanocoffeelounge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/cardanocoffeelounge/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Cardano Coffee lounge in Vietnam # Host weekly coffee meetings to exchange information about Catalyst, Programming on Cardano in a close and friendly environment.
Please stop by to give a comment, like and a vote for this proposal in from the Vietnamese community.
Challenge: F8: Scale-UP Cardano&amp;rsquo;s Community Hubs Proposal: Cardano Coffee lounge in Vietnam Requested Fund: $24800 Meet the Team: # Tien Nguyen Anh # Eastern Townhall co-host Deploying many payment systems for major banks, financial institutions, and telecommunications in Vietnam Founder of the VILAI stake pool, computer science experts, working in the Cardano/Crypto space since 2018.</description></item><item><title>Cardano Forest In Vietnam</title><link>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/cardanoforestinvietnam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/cardanoforestinvietnam/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Cardano Forest In Vietnam # An NFT project to help save the planet by growing trees. In Vietnam, most people know about crypto, but they have a limited understanding of other applications of blockchain ie non-fungible tokens. The solution is to use NFT on Cardano Blockchain to manage the reforestation work in Vietnam.&amp;quot; Please stop by to give a comment, like and a vote for this proposal in from the Vietnamese community.</description></item><item><title>Cardano Hub Indonesia-Video Series</title><link>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/cardanohubvideoseries-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/cardanohubvideoseries-/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Cardano Hub Indonesia-Video Series # Provide 6 high quality educational videos and post in Cardano Indonesia&amp;rsquo;s Official YouTube Channel in Indonesian Language Please stop by and congratulate Mr. Dion on his fantastic proposal.
Challenge: F8: Scale-UP Cardano&amp;rsquo;s Community Hubs Proposal: Cardano Hub Indonesia-Video Series Requested Fund: 18120 Meet the Team: # Dion Setyotomo
Project Manager Business Development Cardano Indonesia Community Manager Eastern Hemisphere Town Hall member Discord admin for Cardano Indonesia Community LinkedIn</description></item><item><title>Cardano SAY NO Plastic Straws | C4O</title><link>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/cardanosaynoplasticstraws/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/cardanosaynoplasticstraws/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Cardano SAY NO Plastic Straws | C4O # We produce straws from natural grass to replace plastic straws. The goal of reducing waste is plastic straws into the environment and ocean.
Please vote for this fantastic plan that uses blockchain to aid with the conservation of the environment, particularly marine life.
Challenge: Miscellaneous Challenge Proposal: Cardano SAY NO Plastic Straws | C4O Requested Fund: $40012 Meet the Team: # We have members who have set up start-ups and are experts in IT and eco-friendly products.</description></item><item><title>Challenge &amp; Scouted for Students 🎓</title><link>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/challengescoutedstudents/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/challengescoutedstudents/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Challenge &amp;amp; Scouted for Students 🎓 # Please stop by to give a comment, like and a vote for this proposal in from the Vietnamese community.
Most student entrepreneurs are suffering from resource shortages, especially in funding and engineer recruitment.
Challenge: Fund9 challenge setting Proposal: Challenge &amp;amp; Scouted for Students 🎓 Requested Fund: 100000 Meet the Team: # Issa Ichikawa 21-year-old/Junior at Waseda University in Japan/Student entrepreneur/Catalyst Fund6 raiser/Catalyst CA/Catalyst Fund6 Challenge Team Member (Connecting Japan Community)</description></item><item><title>DeFi should be more fun on Scaling/MetaVerse/Play</title><link>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/defishouldbemorefun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/defishouldbemorefun/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Make Content More Fun to Learn Easy # Please stop by to give a comment, like and a vote for this proposal in from the Vietnamese community.
A fantastic proposals for game lovers, please vote for the team to make his adventure come true!
Challenge: Gamers On - Chained
Proposal: METAVERSE OF PLAY-TO-ENTERTAIN GAMER
Requested Fund: 137417
Challenge: Gamers On - Chained
Proposal: HQ GRAPHIC FOR MIVERSE METAVERSE</description></item><item><title>FIMI-Vietnamese Cardano Talk</title><link>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/fimivietnamesecardanotalk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/fimivietnamesecardanotalk/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - FIMI-Vietnamese Cardano Talk # Please stop by to give a comment, like and a vote for this proposal in from the Vietnamese community.
How to raise awareness among Vietnamese about Cardano so that it can be adopted into real life in 2022 and after that?
Build a rewarding mechanism to encourage members to find out the news, documents of Cardano, then present them to the community every week.</description></item><item><title>Haskell Book Vietnamese/Japanese Translation</title><link>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/haskellbookvietnamesejapanesetranslation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/haskellbookvietnamesejapanesetranslation/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Haskell Book Vietnamese/Japanese Translation # Japanese/ Vietnamese Subtitle supported, Please stop by to give a comment, like and a vote for this proposal in from the Vietnamese community.
Cardano&amp;rsquo;s Smart Contract is built on Haskell. But there is no book or document about Haskell for developers in Japan\
Challenge: Developer Ecosystem Proposal: Haskell Book Japanese Translation Requested Fund: 9,250 Cardano&amp;rsquo;s Smart Contract is built on Haskell. But there is no book or document about Haskell for developers in Vietnam</description></item><item><title>Haskell Course For Beginner/ Vietnamese</title><link>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/haskellcoursebeginnerviet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/ca-tv/ca-tv-fund8/haskellcoursebeginnerviet/</guid><description>Catalyst TV - Haskell Book Vietnamese/Japanese Translation # Japanese/ Vietnamese Subtitle supported, Please stop by to give a comment, like and a vote for this proposal in from the Vietnamese community.
There are many people who really want to write smart contracts and build projects on Cardano. But Haskell is a big barrier for beginners
Challenge: Developer Ecosystem Proposal: Haskell Course For Beginners Requested Fund: 11580 There are many developers who are very interested in building projects on Cardano but there are not any Haskell courses in Vietnamese.</description></item></channel></rss>