<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Challenges fund 7 on</title><link>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/</link><description>Recent content in Challenges fund 7 on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/catalyst/fund7/challenges/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title> Catalyst Accelerator &amp; Mentors</title><link>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/catalyst-accelerator-mentors/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/catalyst-accelerator-mentors/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $500,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Campaign Brief # Startup innovation and co-creation is the lifeblood of Cardano. Many early stage ventures are now launching into the Cardano ecosystem and Catalyst wants to fuel many pioneering successes.
More needs to be done to accelerate best of breed Catalyst-funded projects by providing pathways into professional business support, investment, and mentoring programmes.
This is important to Catalyst because great ideas need to be nurtured and small teams need access to timely expertise and tools beyond those that they have in-house.</description></item><item><title>Catalyst Natives COTI: Pay with ADA Plug-in</title><link>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/catalyst-native-coti/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/catalyst-native-coti/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $100,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas
Campaign Brief # COTI has developed, together with a very productive and successful partnership with Cardano, a very user-friendly and scalable ADA payment solution for the community. As a result, different online merchants, from a small hotel in Europe to a big e-commerce website in Asia, can easily accept hundreds or thousands of ADA transactions when integrating ADA Pay into their site.</description></item><item><title>A.I. &amp; SingularityNet a $5T market</title><link>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/ai-singularitynet/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/ai-singularitynet/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $500,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideasand Git Repository and Git Book
Campaign Brief # Artificial Intelligence will be a driving force this century. It will be at least as big as cryptocurrencies and blockchains.
The Singularity community has put their trust in Cardano by voting overwhelmingly to risk the value of their AGI tokens by issuing new AGI tokens based on Cardano and moving swiftly from Ethereum to Cardano.</description></item><item><title>Accelerate Decentralized Identity</title><link>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/accelerate-decentralized-id/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/accelerate-decentralized-id/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $425,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Campaign Brief # Our challenge is an evolution of the mass decentralized identity (DID) adoption challenge from Funding Round 6, connecting everything we are learning with the first Atala PRISM Pioneer Program cohort.
The second cohort of the Atala PRISM Pioneer Program will kick off once Catalyst Fund 7 is complete. Between now and then, any member of the Catalyst Community inspired to write a proposal will get access to the Atala PRISM Pioneer Program first cohort course materials on Canvas.</description></item><item><title>Boosting Cardano's DeFi</title><link>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/boost-cardanos-defi/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/boost-cardanos-defi/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $500,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideasand Git Repository and Git Book
Campaign Brief # The previous challenge(ScaleUP Cardano&amp;rsquo;s DeFi Ecosystem) demonstrated success and allowed popular DeFi projects such as Liqwid Finance, Minswap and ErgoDEX to be funded by the treasury, without the participation of venture capitals and with fair launch models, allowing sustainable distribution of the supply among the community/userbase.
The fact that ERGODEX&amp;rsquo;s proposal was the second best voted proposal in the Left-Over budget is an important indicator to demonstrate the competitiveness of the proposals presented in Fund5.</description></item><item><title>Catalyst - Rapid Funding Mechanisms</title><link>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/catalyst-rapid-funding/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/catalyst-rapid-funding/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $250,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas and Git Repository and Git Book
Campaign Brief # Increasing the speed of funding is critically important to allow important projects to move rapidly from volunteers to paid professionals. While volunteerism is strong in our community (and a strength), the ability to pay people for their time will accelerate and dramatically improve the time and energy people will be able to devote to Catalyst.</description></item><item><title>Community Events</title><link>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/community-events/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/community-events/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $200,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideasand Git Repository and Git Book
Campaign Brief # There are already many community-driven events taking place in the wider Catalyst community and this challenge will ensure that these efforts remain sustainable. Since most of the fund distribution for Fund 7 is decided by the community, we as a community have to create this challenge for ourselves.
These events are important and critical for the success of Catalyst because they are bringing the community together and they introduce and onboard new people to our ecosystem.</description></item><item><title>Connecting Japan/日本 Community</title><link>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/connect-japan-community/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/connect-japan-community/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $50,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas and Git Repository and Git Book
Campaign Brief # The goal of this challenge is to find ways to further engage the Japanese community and to help create ways for the Japanese and English speaking community to connect. Proposers are encouraged to propose in Japanese and the Challenge team will help promote the CA role in the Eastern Town hall or equivalent event.</description></item><item><title>DAOs ❤ Cardano</title><link>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/daos-love-cardano/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/daos-love-cardano/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $500,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideasand Git Repository and Git Book
Campaign Brief # Currently if a DAO (even one that is aimed to build products and services around Cardano) wants to setup their DAO infrastructure, the current options are all based on, mostly, the Ethereum blockchain.
These dApps range from basic Treasury management, to Decision making in DAOs and even supporting services like Decentralized Justice.</description></item><item><title>DApps - Integrations</title><link>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/dapps-intergration/campaign-brief/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/catalyst/fund7/challenges/dapps-intergration/campaign-brief/</guid><description>Fund Size: $250,000 USD paid in Ada
Campaign page and browse ideas.
Why is it Important? # Quality Dapps and integrations will increase utility &amp;amp; adoption of Cardano.
How does success look like? # Novel and viable applications get built of top of Cardano attracting users. Integrations manage to pull in more adoption.
Key Metrics to measure # To assess the challenge we will be asking ourselves: Did our efforts manage to attract users to the platform?</description></item></channel></rss>